This... is the ocean?
Sinbad, I was actually frightened.
What if the realities
of the outside world...
disappointed me? What would I do?
But that's all gone now.
I want to know more about the world!
So, where are we heading to next?
Yeah, about that...
We're heading to another small country,
like Sasan.
We were finally approved to enter
the most secluded of the secluded regions.
Ruled by a noble war princess,
it's a matrilineal nation.
A municipality of the sky,
the Artemyra Kingdom.
The Artemyra Kingdom is located
in the southeast region of the continent.
It is a prominent small country,
comparable to the Sasan Kingdom.
Excluding the Dark Continent,
their territory includes
the world's largest valley.
Everything was obscured
and isolated from the outside world.
Why?
Unreal.
Its vast terrain rejects and discourages
any outside visitors.
Shall we start preparing for landing?
It's huge!
Check out that plant!
But it's so humid.
A bird?
Looks like a bird.
But that bird's a little...
It's gigantic.
People?
Impressive size.
It's even wider than this ship.
Look! It's coming back.
Travelers from the outside world?
That's unusual.
Hey there!
What beautiful women...
Guys! If you successfully land
in Artemyra,
I'll show you a good time!
What?!
We'll see how you fare.
Last time, the men couldn't handle
the all-nighter,
trembling like little fawns.
That's all men are good for
so they might as well work hard at it.
So prove us wrong, will you? Good luck!
Yeah, all right.
I'll be looking forward to tonight, then.
Idiot! I wasn't being serious.
Now I'm a lot more excited
to get to Artemyra.
Sinbad, I have a lot more respect for you!
I'll be your follower forever!
Take it easy, Ja'far.
What was that about? He really bugs me.
I thought he was handsome.
Men are all talk anyway!
Let's see if they can make it
through this valley and get to Artemyra.
We gotta pass through this valley today!
Let us discover the Eden of Enchantment!
Yeah! I'm right behind you!
I wouldn't use up all my energy now.
They're full of spirit.
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Why is this happening?!
It's this way! Let's go!
Curse you,
mountain man and ex-assassin!
I can't do this anymore!
It's hot and I'm exhausted!
I refuse to go any farther!
Ja'far, let's take a break here!
What?! Weren't we going
to pass through the valley today?
Oh, how I envy the young...
You're young, too!
Carry me on your back, Hinahoho!
You can carry one or two of me.
Heat... Humidity... Pain...
But I'll endure it...
for my wife and son.
Get it together, let's go!
I'll guide you, so be mindful
of your surroundings and follow me.
Got it, but are you sure?
It's hot and I'm spent...
If he keeps that up...
Don't worry. He's the kind of man
who can do anything.
That's why we cannot spoil him.
Ja'far, you must trust him quite a bit.
You never doubt him.
It's not even about that.
I've seen a lot as his vassal...
I just thought of something brilliant.
I can fly using my Djinn Equip!
Like the ladies
who were flying on that bird!
So, catch you later, fellas!
What was that for, Ja'far?!
Please understand,
we're in Artemyra territory,
where nobody knows
about Djinn Equips or Metal Vessels.
Flying around like that would cause them
to be unnecessarily wary of us.
We'll lose everything!
You're not the only one who's exhausted!
This heat irritates me, too!
Ja'far! That string's too tight!
I'm choking...
Bararaq Sei!
-I'm done.
-Me too. I give up.
Let's take a quick break.
That's...
Artemyra!
The people of this town
live in the tunnels dug into the cliffs.
Yeah.
I see.
They use birds as their main mode
of transportation.
Such a young child...
We face so many unknowns
at our actual destination.
But keep in mind
that we're not here as tourists.
We've exchanged many letters
to be approved for an audience
with the queen.
I would suggest going
to the royal palace now, but...
We stink!
What? An inn? We don't have those here.
We never have any visitors here.
-Oh, no...
-But, guys,
your stench is unbearable!
And that's why I despise men!
Well, is there anywhere we can bathe?
You can perform an ablution
in the river at the bottom of the valley
or go to the red-light district.
Red-light district...
I guess we have to go with the ablution.
Ja'far, don't you think
it would be extremely rude of us
to appear unwashed
in front of the queen?
So...
-let's go to the red-light district!
-Rejected!
Ja'far! So you're saying
it's okay to stink like this?!
We just arrived!
If you cause any trouble with a lady now,
imagine the consequences!
Hinahoho, the red-light district is
a paradise where you're surrounded
by women, right?
I read about it before!
What in the world were you reading?
In any case, do you see all the women
working with such high spirits?
It seems like a good country.
Yes, we hope to establish
a cooperative alliance with them.
Yeah.
We'll settle for the ablution for now.
Yes! Let's get it out of the way.
Excuse me.
Oh, my, forgive me.
What a big lady...
You've come a long way.
Her Excellency is waiting.
This way, please.
Her Excellency is not in her best mood.
Please be mindful of what you say.
Your Excellency,
we are extremely delighted
for the honor
to have an audience with you.
I am Sinbad,
the proprietor of Sindria Company.
It's an international trading company
based in the Reim Empire.
We are here in hopes to establish trade
with your country.
Your Excellency,
do we appear inept in any way?
If something is bothering you...
It's been a while
since I've had male guests.
Go ahead, entertain me.
I am Mira Dianus Artemina,
queen of Artemyra.
Far too many visitors have looked down
on me for being a woman.
That's why I chastise them from the start.
Every one of you is a man.
In letters prior to this meeting,
the company's advisor was
a woman named Rurumu.
She's pregnant right now
so she had to stay behind. Today...
Well, that's a drag. Then leave.
I have no desire to speak to men.
Men are only here to produce
our offspring, that's it.
How can I speak about diplomacy
with such people?
Please, give us a chance.
Enough! I told you to leave.
Please wait, Your Excellency.
I will never betray you.
I only intend to do our best to benefit
this country and Your Excellency.
Please believe me.
Your Excellency.
So, that's how...
you've been seducing women
all over the world, right?
I'm different from other men.
You're wrong.
You're not the only one to say
that you're different from other men.
That's... for me to decide.
Seduction is a man's shallow wit.
I'll show you the terror you'll face
when you deceive women.
You're mistaken!
We never intended to deceive you.
-Take them away.
-Yes!
Can this woman also be...?!
Oh, so you're also a King's Candidate,
master of a Djinn.
A Metal Vessel sorcerer...
You're not just a boor.
But that still doesn't change the fact
that you offended me.
Hey! We don't know
what the others are hiding!
Strip them all!
-What are you doing?!
-Hey, that's...!
Take everything off! All of it!
"Valley of the Dead,"
our country's deepest and darkest.
No one survives this fall.
You shall starve and crumble to dust.
No! I don't want to die here!
Oh, my, look how sturdy you look
without any clothes.
If you return from the valley,
let me show you a good time.
But I doubt you can!
What?
Sin! Guys!
He's powerless,
even as a Metal Vessel sorcerer.
You're one of the Imuchakk,
the tribe of the extreme north.
We'll be examining
your unusual physique.
You're not trying to dissect me, are you?!
-What a great body.
-So burly...
Look at those muscles!
I'll make you experience something
even more terrifying than death.
Hey, is everyone okay?
Yes, seems like we survived it.
My body hurts all over though!
It's a miracle
that we even survived that fall.
We gotta figure out a way back.
That's right! We gotta go back alive!
-Hey, Mystras.
-Yes?
That lady said something before she
pushed you over the cliff, didn't she?
What did she tell you?
What? It was nothing.
No, you're hiding something! I know it!
I'm not hiding anything!
-You are!
-No, I'm not!
-You are! You are!
-No, I'm not! No, I'm not!
Shut it!
Why don't you hide those instead?
Hide what?
Those things that
can't be seen on-screen!
Screen?
The leaves aren't settling in place.
You gotta use a vine to keep it in place.
All right! That's perfect.
Is this acceptable, Ja'far?
I guess so...
All right!
Let's get to searching the area!
Yeah!
It sure is the Valley of the Dead.
This is going to be a struggle to capture.
The surface of the walls are covered
with moss. It's impossible to climb.
There's no sign of animals either.
There's absolutely no way out.
That's right, we haven't eaten anything
since we got to this country.
Actually... I have some emergency food.
Knights of Sasan keep emergency food
in their turbans for times of crisis.
It's a custom to prepare for
the eventuality of being held captive.
Please split it between yourselves.
No, this is yours, Mystras.
You should eat one.
-What? But...
-It's okay.
I was actually starving to death myself.
Thank you.
Delicious!
Ja'far.
This one's yours.
I can't take any food from you...
the youngest one here.
Sin...
Thank you very much, but I'm okay.
During my years as an assassin,
I often went days without food.
Sin, you should eat that jer--
Oh, really? Then I'll eat it!
Hey! What do you think you're doing?!
He said it was mine.
Can't you follow Ja'far's example?!
Aren't you embarrassed as our leader?!
What's that sound?
Wake up, both of you!
Snakes everywhere!
I see various kinds,
large, small and poisonous.
This is like a swamp of snakes!
What should we do?
Ja'far, Mystras! Live on for me!
I wish I could've chosen
my own place of death.
Surrounded by beautiful women,
delicious food, delicious wine,
and other delicious things...
What are you saying?
-What?
-Good grief.
It's unlike you to spill your guts.
You're only acting weak
because you're hungry.
But that's an easy fix!
Let's restore our energy by eating this!
Ja'far...
You're... going to eat that?
I've strangled and eaten many of these
during my assassin years.
It's packed with nutrients,
and as long as we cut the neck,
you can eat the poisonous ones, too.
Let's eat!
Yes!
Take your time, there's plenty of them!
Sinbad and his crew worked
in earnest to survive.
They ate snakes, built fires,
gathered vegetation to construct
a house that kept the rain and wind out.
They worked as the sun rose
and slept when the sun set.
While living a life revolved
around the sun,
their instincts as animals
were coming back.
They then...
successfully adapted...
to this extreme situation.